<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>c&#43;&#43; on Henrick Deschamps</title>
    <link>https://hnrck.io/blog/tags/c&#43;&#43;/</link>
    <description>Recent content in c&#43;&#43; on Henrick Deschamps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Henrick Deschamps</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hnrck.io/blog/tags/c++/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy `C` in modern C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://hnrck.io/blog/posts/2020-06-13-1-legacy-c-in-modern-cpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hnrck.io/blog/posts/2020-06-13-1-legacy-c-in-modern-cpp/</guid>
      <description>[tl;dr] The integration of C in C++ was designed a long time ago and the mechanisms are efficient but spartan, forcing the client code to take care to manage memory and data access. When integrating into modern C++, where there is often a culture of good memory management and pointer manipulation, these mechanisms are not comfortable. There are solutions to interface C code more cleanly, through OOP or or C++ smart pointers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern C&#43;&#43; singleton implementation through an example</title>
      <link>https://hnrck.io/blog/posts/2018-11-05-1-modern-cpp-singleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hnrck.io/blog/posts/2018-11-05-1-modern-cpp-singleton/</guid>
      <description>[tl;dr] Modern C++ best practices allows an explicit and beautiful implementation of the singleton design pattern.
 Code source of the full example available on hnrck/singleton_example.
 Table of Contents  Motivations Context Related work  Blogs and websites Books   Introduction  About design patterns The singleton pattern  Why using a singleton How to implement a singleton     The Logger class  The Logger class declaration  Constructor and assignment Copy constructor and assignment Move constructor and assignment   Singleton functionality Logger functionality  Log level Print method Output setting Output protection Logger class final result   Test application  Global parameters Test routine A small exception Main function Test application final result     Experimentation  GitHub repository Compilation Execution   Conclusion  Summary Limitations Future work     Motivations First of all, pardon my French, I am a French native speaker with a fairly solid background in English, and some of my sentences may seem flawed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>